Contact

+79267033464 (Home) gurshumov.david@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/david-gurshumov (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React

JavaScript

Go (Programming Language)

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)

David Gurshumov

Full Stack Developer (Golang / JS / TS)
Tel Aviv

Summary

Hello, my name is David, and I am a Frontend / Full-Stack Developer

I have 3 years of Frontend Experience and the last 6 months working as a Full Stack Developer, the backend language is Golang, also have a small experience with Node.js

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Golang Webpack WebSockets, GraphQL

Frontend:

Frameworks: React, Angular, Vue
HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, LESS
Webpack
RxJs, NgRx, Redux, Thunk, Saga,
CSS-modules, Styled Components
Bootstrap
Animations (CSSTransition, CSS Animate)

Backend

Node.js:

Frameworks: Express, Koa, Nest

Mongoose, Sequelize

Golang: Logrus, Validator, Echo, Unit Tests

REST API, gRPC MongoDB

Docker/Docker-Compose/Nginx

Experience

OZON.ru

Full-stack Developer

October 2021 - Present (8 months)

Creating the Cart / Checkout part of Ozon.ru Marketplace

Frontend:

Vue, TypeScript, WebPack, SCSS

Backend - Golang, Postgres, MemCached

Beeline Russia

Frontend Engineer (Angular, Vue)

October 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Developing of React SPA application

TypeScript, MobX, Styled

WebPack, GraphQL

Before june:

Development of main client app, an Angular SPA, and back office on Vue 2

ООО "Кометрика"

Frontend Engineer

November 2019 - October 2020 (1 year)

Adding new features and legacy code support to government web service -

National Accreditation System

Adding functionality to micro SPA on React

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Angular 2+, React, RxJs
- HTML5/SCSS
- Git, GitLab, TeamCity, Docker

Банк ВТБ 24

Frontend Engineer

August 2019 - October 2019 (3 months)

Москва, Россия

Development of SPA Angular 7 web-application for business client managers

- JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular 7, RxJs
- SCSS, Bootstrap 4

- Git, tfs, agile

Education

Moscow State Institute of Radio Engineering, Electronics and Automation (Technical University)

Bachelor's degree, technical systems · (2015 - 2019)